let savollar7 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "to allow",
        answer: "A. ruxsat bermoq",
        options: [
            "A. ruxsat bermoq",
            "B. taqiqlamoq",
            "C. va'da bermoq",
            "D. cheklamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to announce",
        answer: "B. e'lon qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. bildirmoq",
            "B. e'lon qilmoq",
            "C. ko'rsatmoq",
            "D. aytmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "beside",
        answer: "C. yonma-yon",
        options: [
            "A. ustida",
            "B. ostida",
            "C. yonma-yon",
            "D. oldida"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "challenge",
        answer: "D. qiyinchilik",
        options: [
            "A. imkoniyat",
            "B. fursat",
            "C. muammo",
            "D. qiyinchilik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "to claim",
        answer: "A. tasdiqlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. tasdiqlamoq",
            "B. rad etmoq",
            "C. qabul qilmoq",
            "D. rozi bo'lmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "condition",
        answer: "C. holat",
        options: [
            "A. imkoniyat",
            "B. kattalik",
            "C. holat",
            "D. daraja"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to contribute",
        answer: "B. hissa qo'shmoq",
        options: [
            "A. maslahat bermoq",
            "B. hissa qo'shmoq",
            "C. kelishmoq",
            "D. sarflamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "difference",
        answer: "C. farq",
        options: [
            "A. o'xshashlik",
            "B. umumiylik",
            "C. farq",
            "D. bog'liqlik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "to divide",
        answer: "A. bo'lmoq",
        options: [
            "A. bo'lmoq",
            "B. birlashtirmoq",
            "C. ko'paytirmoq",
            "D. kamaytirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "expert",
        answer: "D. ekspert",
        options: [
            "A. bilimdon",
            "B. havaskor",
            "C. shogird",
            "D. ekspert"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "famous",
        answer: "B. mashhur",
        options: [
            "A. ma'lum",
            "B. mashhur",
            "C. muhim",
            "D. sevimli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "force",
        answer: "A. kuch",
        options: [
            "A. kuch",
            "B. energiya",
            "C. qarshilik",
            "D. bosim"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "harm",
        answer: "C. zarar",
        options: [
            "A. nuqson",
            "B. yetishmovchilik",
            "C. zarar",
            "D. kamchilik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to lay",
        answer: "B. qo'ymoq",
        options: [
            "A. ko'tarmoq",
            "B. qo'ymoq",
            "C. otmoq",
            "D. urmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "peace",
        answer: "D. tinchlik",
        options: [
            "A. urush",
            "B. jang",
            "C. bezovtalik",
            "D. tinchlik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "prince",
        answer: "C. shahzoda",
        options: [
            "A. qirol",
            "B. ritsar",
            "C. shahzoda",
            "D. gersog"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to protect",
        answer: "A. himoya qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. himoya qilmoq",
            "B. hujum qilmoq",
            "C. jarohatlamoq",
            "D. yo'q qilmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "to sense",
        answer: "B. sezmoq",
        options: [
            "A. hidlamoq",
            "B. sezmoq",
            "C. tatib ko'rmoq",
            "D. eshitmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "sudden",
        answer: "A. kutilmagan",
        options: [
            "A. kutilmagan",
            "B. sekin",
            "C. shiddatli",
            "D. doimiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "therefore",
        answer: "D. shu sababli",
        options: [
            "A. shunga qaramay",
            "B. baribir",
            "C. lekin",
            "D. shu sababli"
        ]
    }
];
